hey what's up blitzers I've got some new
exciting updates to announce these
updates will be available once you open
the app you'll have the popup to install
them with one click update number one is
now subtasks are available within the
floating timer so you can see I've got
my live timer on in Blitz mode I can now
expand the subtasks I've got a subtask
preview over here I can add new subtasks
I can reorder subtask I can delete
subtasks as you would be able to
normally uh previously you would only be
able to access access subtask from from
a pause State and now it's always
visible within your floating timer the
only thing the only limitation is that
if a task doesn't already have a subtask
in it you won't be able to uh add new
subtask from within the floating timer
or any live timer even within the panel
State you it has to be in a non-life
state like this one as you can see to
access the subtask uh add option over
here right secondly we do have a really
exciting update drum roll we now have
settings first of all in the that's not
the big feature but we have our settings
within the Navar accessible previously
the settings would be within the uh the
expanded options menu but we brought it
out here just to quickly access them and
tweak uh preferences uh as you would
need them but importantly more
importantly we have theme settings
available in Blitz it now which means
yes you have like mode light mode is
finally available on Blitz it so this uh
allows you to switch between a dark mode
only or a light mode only theme but you
can also switch it to based on system
those are the two main updates there's a
list of other items that we fixed and
proofed which you can go ahead and check
out in our change log the change log
again will be available once you sign
into the app you'll see the popup with
the change log broken down there but you
can also find the change log head over
to our help center and there's a link to
our change log within the help center on
the right hand side
navbar the latest um change log is
Friday November 1st 2024 and these are
the main uh updates we also have
importantly we do have the Windows
security update because we finally
secured our SSL certification which
means that we don't have that warning
screen when you try to install uh Blitz
it on windows so we are officially
Windows approved so that's it for
October's updates hope you guys are
excited about these new uh additions and
we've got more features in the pipeline
so do stay tuned and keep supporting us
within the community giving us your
feedback within Discord and frill uh
this always helps us make better
decisions when it comes to um improving
Blitz it I'll see you guys in a future
video